{
    "id": "838e04a9eb2f46d88c3b16f273c1a32b",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t you ……………… listen to what I say?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "27186d0500bd48f7a2d011ac7dfcdc30"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… matters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Nothing",
                "Not anything"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "25cbc012d4114ecf8fbb493b4aace267"
        },
        {
            "question": "I opened the door, but I …………… see nobody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "couldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "426a2649c8c740f2a8d0a7c33c974c78"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of my brothers …………….. here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37d1a726e89e43c68a327563b631ed6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ruth didn’t turn up, and James didn’t ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec6ba2706f4b494e89e9890db740508b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was only talking like that because she ………………. nervous.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9f190e2cf714f919867ccc41db2216e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have only ………………. to India once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88c30ccd503945ceb7f6e73bcb1ecd25"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… given a medal for living with her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ought be",
                "ought to be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5a6a6630b67a409582cd0a3475d13986"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ran ……………….. the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "out of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4f18ce8c5b3c406795e18e059696fb83"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has got no ideas of ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "his own"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e46600ae43ab465eb7d491af599a438a"
        }
    ]
}